In Antarctica, you're never allowed to
pee on the ice, not even when you're
hiking for hours. It's because it's so
cold and so dry there that when it
snows, it basically never melts. So, it
just stacks up into layers and layers of
ice and traps air inside. And then
scientists drill ice cores to study that
air going back hundreds of thousands of
years to learn what the environment was
like back then. But if anything else
hits that ice, like ash from volcanic
eruptions, that gets trapped, too. So,
you can't pee because if you did,
>> one day some descendant of yours would
be taking an ice core in Antarctica and
they'd dig and dig and dig and they'd
pull it out and they'd say, "What's that
yellow line?" But to see what's really
hidden under the ice, subscribe because
it's really